Haloo shabbb

Untuk CV lu memberikan kesan yang bagus, karna keliatan nya padet. Struktur lu jg bagus ngeliatin work experience dulu, itu penting karna lu ngehighlight lu adalah orng yang berpengalaman. Deskripsi poin poin lu juga bagus, lu bisa mengemas diri lu dengan baik

ada beberapa hal hal kecil yang menurut gw perlu dibenerin,liat di halaman selanjutnya ya

Overview agak dibenerin urutannya

Setelah lu cerita interest lu, dibandingin cerita tentang yg student association lebih baik ceritain kalo lu udh pernah 2 kali intern , kalo ditotalin udh lebih dari 8 bulan pengalaman KERJA, lalu langsung ke two times being assistant lecturer in several courses

Work experience coba urutannya, kerja profesional lalu assistant lecturer karna ntar yg diharepin pertama kali itu lu pernah kerja ga, bkn lu pernah ngajar ga, tapi assistant lecturer itu penting jg biar nunjukin kalo lu seolah olah "paling baik" di mata kuliah itu sehingga dipercaya, dan juga nunjukin lu bisa handle banyak orng. Jadi tetep, pengalaman kerja dulu yg di atas

Organizational Experience tapi lu ga nyebutin nama organisasinya, cuma yg HMSI doang

Sebutin yaa!, karna they have no idea dengan apa yg lu tulis kalo lu ngga perjelas, anggaplah mereka baru pertama baca & ga ngerti apa apa, jgn asumsi "ah mereka ngerti lah arahnya kesini"

Oke mungkin itu revisi dari gw, terbilang revisi minor. Kalo misal gw jadi lu gw benerin gitu, tapi balik lagi ke lu ya, misalnya yg lu buat udh pas menurut lu yowes pd pake yg versi lu

sejauh ini, gw puas liat cv lu, bagusss, kalo diliat dari keseluruhan, layak dapet interview... mungkin lu jg abis nyiapin cv ini buat portfolio dlm bentuk pdf yaa, buat nunjukin project2 lu yg udh lu buat pas nanti interview....buat dari skrng soalnya ntar dipanggil interview itu dadakan, jd jgn dadakan jg bikinnya

ok goodluck ya shabbbbb!

SHABBRINA

+62 8951393600 · ishabbrina@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/shabbrina-793b2624b

undergraduate aja, semester 4 itu melemahkan Iu, bakal dipandang remeh kalau dibandingin sm semester 6 I am an active 4th semester student at Bakrie University, majoring in Information Systems, with a main interest in numbers, data analysis, maintenance and development. Has a special interest in roles as a Web Developer, System Developer, and UI Designer in the IT field. I am active in campus activities, including playing a role in the Student Association and being on the committee for major campus events for the admission of new students for 2 periods. and am as an assistant lecturer in the information systems design analysis course feaching 2 classes, namely, regular and employee classes at Bakrie University.

WORK EXPERIENCES

kalimatnya lebih baki jgn di akhir paragraf, setelah lu jelasin interest lu aia

Mar 2024 - Present

Laceto

BAKRIE UNIVERSITY

Assistant Lecturer, Information System Design Analysis Course

- Led 10 practical sessions over 20 hours, with 36 regular students attending and 19 employee students attending, fostering understanding and application of information systems analysis and design.
- Created extensive educational modules covering various topics such as introduction to UI and UX, Introduction to Figma, Prototypes in figma, Plugin Features in figma and introduction to UML (Use Case, Activity Diagram).
- Collaborated closely with course instructors to ensure seamless integration of practical sessions with lecture content and learning objectives.
- Acted as a primary resource for students, offering guidance and clarification on practical exercises and course materials.
- Assessed student assignments and provided constructive feedback to reinforce comprehension and application of design analysis infromation system.
- Produced thorough reports detailing student performance and progression for the benefit of course instructors.

BAKRIE UNIVERSITY

Assistant Lecturer, Algorithms and Programming Course

- Conducted 10 practical sessions for 20 hours, with 45 students actively involved in learning the basics of the python programming language.
- Developed comprehensive educational modules covering topics such as Basic Python, Dictionary, Function, OOP (object oriented programming), Pandas, OOP Methodologies and Matplotlib.
- Collaborate closely with course instructors to ensure alignment of practice sessions with course content and learning objectives, thereby enhancing student understanding.
- Provide invaluable support to students, offering guidance and clarification regarding practical exercises and course materials.
- Evaluated student assignments meticulously, delivering constructive feedback to reinforce understanding and application of Algorithms and Programming.
- Generated detailed reports documenting student performance and progress, facilitating informed decisions by course instructors.







BAKRIE UNIVERSITY

Oct 2023 - Feb 2024

System Developent and Web Development

- · Developing the Bakrie University Main Website and creating an English version of the website.
- Developing websites for all study programs and creating English language versions of websites
- Create a UBakrie Press Website using CMS.
- Create Bakrie University BIG Mobile Apps UI using Fights
- Manage all websites to run well and back up all websites regularly.
- Push Code from repository to SSH.

Feb 2021 - May 20

DANA PENSIUN BANK INDONESIA

Quality Assurance

- Analyze user needs and understand the pusiness goals to be achieved through the helpdesk web platform.
- Collect, analyze, and interpret data related to help desk web usage and performance.
- Identifies improvement opportunities and develops appropriate solution recommendations to improve web helpdesk functionality and efficiency.
- Work closely with development teams and other technical teams to ensure timely and quality implementation of solutions.
- Provide training and support to web helpdesk users in optimizing platform use.
- Perform continuous monitoring of web helpdesk performance, identify problems, and coordinate necessary corrective actions.

EDUCATION

BAKRIE UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Information System

Sep 2022 - Present

- chelor of illiorniation system
- Current GPA: 3.68
- · Staff Of Academic Departments Information Systems Student Association
- Staff Of Event Division Ubakrie's Week
- Assistant Lecturer for Information Systems Analysis and Design Courses

SMK NEGERI 71 JAKARTA

Jul 2019 - Apr 2022

Vocational High School Software Engineering

- GPA: 89.78
- Achieved the top position in academic performance among all students in the graduating class, securing the prestigious title of "Rank 2nd in Paralel".
- Highest score achiever Average Report Card Semester 1-6 Competency Level Software Engineering Skills.
- As the first best student at SMKN 71 Jakarta.
- Amanah as Deputy Chair (OSIS) 2019/2020, leading initiatives to represent the student organization and encourage positive change in the school community.
- Amanah as Public Relations 1 (OSIS) 2020/2021, leading initiatives, providing ideas in work
 programs actively and creatively full of innovation to represent student organizations and
 encourage positive change in the school community.
- As a class secretary, you are responsible for assisting the teacher in daily administration, creating agendas for class meetings or socialization, handling communication between teachers and students.

 Actively participate in competitions including storytelling and speech competitions, honing language skills and public speaking skills.

Organizational Experience

Staff of Academic Department, Information System Student Association Oct 2023 - Present

- Mandate as Department Secretary, responsible for the report of the person in charge of each department's work program.
- Actively involved as a member of HMSI, supporting activities aimed at enhancing students' academic and professional experiences.
- Mandate as a member of the events division for student orientation activities for the information systems study program, including drafting MOUs, TORs, and event rundowns...
- Mandate as member of the Public Relations division for academic seminars on machine learning, including Poster Design, Content Ideas, Google Form Seminar.
- Mandate as the Head of event for an academic seminar on machine learning, including drafting MOUs, TORs, and event rundowns.
- Participate in contributing to ScholarSIF, a pre-exam program that aims to help students prepare for exams, and is trusted to act as a facilitator.

Staff Of Event Division

Mei 2023 - Present

- Responsible for planning, implementing and evaluating events within the framework of Ubakries Week 2023/2024.
- Coordinate time to ensure the smooth implementation of the event, including selecting the location, schedule and necessary equipment.
- Actively participate in preparation and evaluation meetings to improve event quality and participant satisfaction.
- Address challenges and issues proactively during event execution to ensure optimal attendee experience.
- Communicate effectively with various related parties, including committee members, participants and vendors, to ensure all needs are met properly.
- Successfully running the event in 2023 with a total of 850++

Vice Chairman (OSIS)

Jul 2019 - Jul 2020

- Assist the Student Council President in guiding members, monitoring their performance and representing student interests.
- Able to back up the chair in leading meetings, facilitating discussions, and collaborating with board members to address student issues and implement initiatives.
- Collaborate with MPK members to organize events, projects and campaigns that enrich student lives and increase school spirit.

Public Relation (OSIS)

Jul 2020 - Jul 2021

- Responsible for OSIS internal and external communications to students and school staff.
- Promoted school events through social media campaigns which succeeded in increasing student participation by 20%.
- Manage relationships with local media and obtain coverage for school events helds
- Design and deliver presentations to students and school staff about OSIS activities.
- Lead the team to prepare quality and regular OSIS activity reports.